contestburner.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Contest Burner

## Privacy Policy

**This privacy statement applies to the website of:**

http://www.contestburner.com  
12235 Beach Blvd. Suite 206  
Stanton, CA 90680  
US

We respect your privacy. This is why we have taken the time to disclose our information collection practices and our privacy policy. Please take the time to review this document.

**Of the information we do collect, we allow our visitors the following access to the information.**

  * The contest Username you specify when you create a contestant account at any contest powered by ContestBurner.
  * A link to your Facebook, Twitter, YouTube or other social media accounts you have connected to your contestant account.
  * The number of points you have attained in each contest you have entered.
  * The website does not collect any other data that can identify its visitors.

**We collect information for the following purpose(s):**

  * Research and development.
  * Building records of visitors without linking identifying information to the records for the purpose of research, analysis and reporting.
  * Creating, editing, tracking and administering contests both on our site, on clients sites and within a variety of social media sites.

**Who has access to the information we collect?**

Ourselves and/or our agents which utilize the information only for the purpose given. _Information is only shared with our partners who share our privacy policy. Public contests will share the contest information with the general public on their web pages.  
_

**How long is information kept?**

Information is retained for an indeterminate period of time.

If you believe that our website has collected incorrect information or if you would like to dispute any information, please contact us using the address at the top of this page.

**Social Media Authentication & Authorization**

Sites like Facebook & Twitter allow ContestBurner to better track and administer a contest utilizing customized “apps”. If you authorize the ContestBurner app at any social media website you are sharing your information & access to your account with ContestBurner.  We will only display or utilize this information in reference to the contests that you have joined or that you might be interested in.  This information is not used for any other purpose.

If you have installed ContestBurner software on your server, on your Facebook page or elsewhere in order to create & run a contest we will require authentication of our app in order to use certain functionality. This will be used exclusively to run the contests you create.
